Thi Thu Hang Chung

Salisbury Downs SA 5108 | 0497 223 359 | ctth1302@gmail.com | LinkedIn

Profile

Dynamic and growth-focused professional with strong educational background and 7 years of experience in overseeing project and customer service activities to achieve and exceed predefined performance targets. Possesses resourceful knowledge about software programming and designing to enhance operational efficiency. Looking to utilize project management and customer service skills in combination with software developing skill to start new journey in IT industry.

Key Skills

- Software Development: Java, JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, jQuery, MySQL, PHP
- Project Management: Jira
- Customer Service and Support: Kayako
- Key Strengths:
 - Communication
 - Collaboration
 - Time management
 - Team leadership
 - Problem solving
 - Patience
 - Multitasking
 - Adaptability

Employment History

GEM Solution, Adelaide, Australia

Web Developer

November 2022 – February 2023

- Worked with a team of experienced developers and designers to bring to life innovative and dynamic websites and web applications.
- Honed skills in Wix, Velo's APIs, Shopify, and front-end development.
- Wix: created custom Wix websites for small business, integrated Velo's APIs to add functionality and enhance the user experience on the website.
- Shopify: gained hands-on experience in setting up and customizing Shopify stores using Shopify Liquid and CSS.
- Front-end Development: built responsive and interactive web pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript and React.

VMSoftware, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

February 2016 - December 2019

ICT Account Manager

- Mentored new staff members to enhance professional capabilities.
- Allocated accurate module for all account to manage key accounts.
- Monitored new and ongoing projects to streamline operations.
- Interacted with client to understand business needs and advice best recommendations.
- Liaised with senior management to enhance service efficiency, while coordinating with cross-departmental teams to ensure smooth regulations.

VMSoftware, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia Truong Dung Tourism Co., Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

September 2014 – January 2016 August 2013 – August 2014

ICT Customer Service Team Leader

- Oversaw Customer Support agents to deliver the best service.
- Liaised with project manager and cross-functional teams to assure smooth regulations of project.
- Coached newly hired staff to boost workforce capacity.
- Assisted customer by mentoring knowledge about product use to enhance customer satisfaction.
- Guaranteed smooth circulation of information by accurately delivering company's message or announcement to correct member's group.

Education

Master of Information Technology

December 2021

Flinders University, South Australia Major: Information Technology

Degree Related Projects

RSPCA Court Summons App Using Docassemble Platform

February 2021 – June 2021

Project URL: RSPCA Automation App

Key learnings:

- Developed app using Python and Docassemble platform to assist RSPCA's (The Royal Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals South Australia Incorporated) legal counsel on preparing Information and Summons documents efficiently before court.
- Developed and performed UX Test for the app utilizing SEQs (Single Ease Questions) and SUS's (System Usability Scales) to evaluate the app performance.
- Presented the app to client to deliver its functionality and usability.
- Graded HD for the whole project and received positive feedbacks from RSPCA's representative.

Master of Commerce December 2012

Swinburne University of Technology, Victoria

Major: International Business

Bachelor of Economics August 2010

Foreign Trade University, Ho Chi Minh City

Major: International Business

Professional Year Program

Current

ACS / Navitas, South Australia

Qualifications and Memberships

ACS Professional Association member

March 2022

Referees

Referees are available upon request.